ChandIer, you're doing so weII
with this whoIe getting married...
...never gonna sIeep with anyone for the
rest of your Iife thing. I thinks it's great.
-Hey. Who wants French toast?
-I'II have some.
Me too. Eggs and miIk in the fridge.
Thanks.
-What's the matter?
-My hand feeIs weird.
I guess it's because I'm engaged!
-When wiII that start getting annoying?
-Start?
Let's start the wedding pIans.
-Okay.
-AIready?
We got a Iot to do. We gotta think
about the fIowers, the music--
-I have thoughts on the music--
-ChandIer. Too many cooks.
Take it from me. AII you have to do
is show up and try to say the right name.
-What in God's name is that?
-Oh, my God, the wedding book?
I haven't seen that since fourth grade.
This baby has everything.
Take, you know, Iocations, for instance:
First organized aIphabeticaIIy,
then geographicaIIy...
...then by square footage.
That is so smart.
Break it off. Break it off now.
Look, here's the invitation you used to your
wedding to John Lynch in the fifth grade.
Remember how I got sick
and Ross had to fiII in as a bridesmaid?
I was a brides-boy.
I don't smeII French toast, brides-boy.
The One With RacheI's Book
That concIusiveIy proves...
...that I had the idea
for Jurassic Park first.
Let's take a Iook--
Phoebe, what are you doing here?
I need to taIk to you. It's urgent.
It's about Monica and ChandIer.
Oh, my God. Of course.
WouId you pIease excuse me
for a moment?
Do you know each other's hometowns?
Why don't you...?
What's going on?
WeII, not much. I was just thinking
that since they just got engaged...
...it wouId be nice
if they have privacy.
So couId I just move in with you
for a coupIe days?
Okay, sure. But what's wrong
with Monica and ChandIer?
Nothing. Why?
Phoebe, you said it was urgent.
Yeah, it is.
My movie starts in, Iike, five minutes.
Do you reaIize I have a cIassroom
fuII of students?
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm so rude.
Does anyone want to come to the movies?
I haven't cIeared the
budget with my parents...
...but teII me how this is for music:
A string quartet for the processionaI,
a jazz trio for cocktaiIs...
...the Bay City RoIIers
for dancing....
Wait, that was
for my sixth grade wedding.
You couIdn't get them anyway.
Ian doesn't even pIay anymore and Derek....
Derek is a name I shouIdn't know.
Mon, do you have another piIIow,
something a IittIe snuggIier?
Why are you napping here
instead of at your pIace?
-The duck.
-What-- The duck?
What the heII
did the damn duck do now?
WeII, he did not get sick
somewhere in there...
...and it was immediateIy found
and properIy cIeaned up.
Do I get to Iook at this book...
...or is it just for peopIe
invoIved in the wedding?
Of course you can Iook at it.
I want your opinion.
Here you go.
-What about centerpieces?
-Centerpieces!
-Roses or IiIies?
-DefiniteIy roses.
I think they're more ''wedding-y.''
-But IiIies are the cIear choice.
-Oh, my God, it's Iike one mind.
Guys, guys, you gotta Iet me nap.
I'm gonna get cranky.
Joey, there's a perfectIy good couch
across the haII.
Yes, it is perfectIy good...
...and it is not one of the pIaces
the duck got sick.
What?
-AII right, I'm gonna go.
-Joey, what did the duck do?
I don't know,
but he did not eat your face cream.
Hey, IittIe buddy. How you feeIing?
What the heII is in that face cream?
That's so soft.
PiIIowcases!
''Zelda looked at the chimney sweep.
Her father, the vicar-- ''
Vicar?
''--wouldn't be home for hours.
Her loins were burning.
She threw caution to the wind
and reached out and grabbed his-- ''
This is a dirty book!
Phoebe?
Oh, Ross, hi.
-Phoebe, what are you doing?
-Sorry, I'm with a cIient right now.
-Phoebe!
-Okay, Iet's taIk outside.
UnfortunateIy, this time wiII be counted
as part of your massage.
So try...
...and think reIaxing thoughts.
And don't touch any of my dinosaurs.
I know they're cooI, but they're mine.
Phoebe, you can't massage peopIe
in my apartment.
I did it at Monica and ChandIer's.
And they knew about it?
Okay, Ross, what is this reaIIy about?
This is my home and I want to be
abIe to come and go when I want.
I wiII find somepIace eIse
to do the rest of my appointments.
I don't know what the big deaI is.
I don't want naked,
greasy strangers in my apartment...
...when I want to kick back
with a puzzIe-- Beer, coId beer.
Hey, Joey. What are you doing?
Sweeping. Why?
Does it turn you on?
No.
What if I was sweeping a chimney?
Joey, did you eat my face cream?
Where are you going?
The vicar won't be home for hours.
Joey, where did you Iearn that word?
Where do you think...
...ZeIda?
-You found my book?!
-Yeah, I did!
Joey, what are you doing
going into my bedroom?
I'm sorry. I went in there to take a nap.
I know I shouIdn't have, but you got porn!
God! I cannot beIieve you invaded
my privacy Iike that!
ZeIda.
Now, you seem a IittIe tense. Maybe
you'II reIax if I gave you a nice miIk bath.
Okay, you know what?
-I don't even Iike that part.
-Oh, I do.
You know what? I don't care.
I'm not ashamed of my book.
There's nothing wrong with a woman
enjoying a IittIe erotica.
It's just a heaIthy expression
of femaIe sexuaIity...
...which, by the way, is something
that you wiII never understand.
You got porn.
-HeIIo.
-Hi, is Phoebe here?
-No, she's out for the night.
-Oh, great.
Can I heIp you with something?
I don't know. Are you a masseur?
Yes, I am.
Great! Dad?
Thank you so much.
I'II pick him up in an hour.
You need heIp with that?
Your parents must've been thriIIed
when you toId them you were engaged.
Oh, yeah.
I shouId probabIy caII them.
I remember when we first got engaged.
-I've never heard that story.
-Dad, you don't--
WeII, I'd gotten Judy pregnant.
I stiII don't know how.
You don't know how? Your dog
thought my diaphragm was a chew toy.
What a sweet story.
At Ieast you're not hearing it
at your fifth grade HaIIoween party.
They wanted a scary story.
We're reaIIy excited
about our wedding pIans.
I guess pretty soon we'II be making a big
withdrawaI from the Monica wedding fund.
-What?
-You teII her, Jack. I can't do it.
You have the wedding fund, don't you?
We have it.
OnIy, now we caII it ''the beach house.''
You spent my wedding
fund on the beach house?
We're sorry. We assumed...
...that if you got married after 30
you'd pay for it yourseIf.
You bought the beach house
when I was 23.
So you've had seven years
of beach fun...
...and you can't put a price on that.
We do feeI bad about this.
We saved again
when you dated Richard...
...then that went to heII,
so we redid the kitchen.
What about ChandIer?
It was ChandIer.
We didn't think he'd propose.
CIearIy I did not start drinking
enough at the start of the meaI.
I can't beIieve there's no money
for my wedding.
Maybe, if your father hadn't tried...
...to seII ice over the Internet.
-It seemed Iike such a simpIe idea.
-Stupid, Jack. The word is stupid.
Enough. I don't want
to hear about it anymore.
Good Iuck, ChandIer.
Okay, now I'm going to...
...touch you.
That's soft.
Why does Joey keep taIking
about chimney sweeps and vicars?
I thinks he's just been rehearsing
for an episode of his show.
Because it reaIIy sounds
Iike a bad porn noveI.
Do you think your parents
couId heIp pay for it?
I don't know.
My mother spent most of her money
on her fourth wedding.
She's saving the rest for her divorce.
And any extra cash my father has
he saves for his yearIy trips to...
...DoIIywood.
-What happened at dinner?
-My parents spent the wedding fund.
My God, what did you order?
Wait, there's no money?
WeII, this is terribIe.
You guys are gonna have to get
married in, Iike, a rec center.
Oh, my God, you're right.
We're gonna have to be out by 6 so they
can take out the fIoor for senior swim.
-Honey, it's gonna be okay.
-No, it's not gonna be okay.
-No swing band, no IiIies.
-No, but that's good.
You don't want IiIies.
If a cat ate them, it wouId die.
-What?
-I'm just saying, now you couId invite cats.
It's gonna be okay.
I mean, you don't need to have this...
...rustic ItaIian feast.
You don't need this custom-made...
...empire-waisted, duchess satin gown.
You can wear off-the-rack.
It's reaIIy gonna be okay.
The important thing is that we Iove each
other and we're gonna get married.
Do you even understand what
''off-the-rack'' means?
Why don't you pay for it yourseIf?
How? I don't have any money.
-WeII, I have some.
-How much?
WeII, cIose to....
-Are you kidding me?!
-How much?
-Enough for wedding scenario A.
-ReaIIy?
Scenario A has IiIies. Someone's gonna have
to break it to the cats and it won't be me.
How great are you, you IittIe saver!
This is exactIy
the budget of my dream wedding.
You guys are so made for each other.
You're not suggesting that we spend
aII of the money on the wedding?
Yeah.
Look, Mon, I've been saving this money
for six years...
...and I kind of had some of it earmarked
for the future, not just for a party.
HeIIo, Mr. ChandIer.
Sweetie, this is the most speciaI day
of our Iives.
I reaIize that, honey, but I'm not gonna
spend aII the money on one party.
Honey, I Iove you.
But if you caII our wedding
a party one more time...
...you may not get invited.
We can aIways earn more money.
We're onIy gonna get married once.
I understand, but I have to put
my foot down. The answer is no.
You're gonna have to ''put your foot down''?
Yes, I am.
Money and a firm hand.
FinaIIy a ChandIer I can get on board with.
-Hey, Rach.
-Joey.
Hey, Rach, do you smeII smoke?
I get it. Smoke, chimney,
chimney sweep. Very funny. Ha, ha.
No, no, I'm serious.
You don't smeII it?
Something's on fire.
No, I don't smeII anything.
Oh, you know what? It's probabIy
just your burning Ioins.
-Hey, what are you guys taIking about?
-Nothing.
Damn, this coffee's coId.
Do you mind if I heat this up
on your Ioins?
You know, I cannot beIieve
you toId him. Joey....
So I guess you bought that book
after we broke up.
Yeah, I did, because I wore out
my first copy when I was with you.
Oh, yeah?
WeII, when we were going out,
I read tons of porno magazines.
What's up?
Ross, how couId you do that
to an oId man?
Excuse me, Iadies.
I'm sorry?
My massage cIient, Arthur.
His daughter said some guy
that worked for me...
...gave him a reaIIy weird massage.
I gave him an extremeIy
professionaI massage.
He said you poked
at him with wooden spoons.
Okay, so it wasn't
a traditionaI massage.
But I did give him acupressure
with a pair of chopsticks...
...and I gentIy exfoIiated him
with a mop.
WeII, he's never coming back.
You just cost me $80 a week.
This is your fauIt.
You didn't move his appointment.
Oh, it's my fauIt?
You didn't have to massage him.
You couId've sent him away.
You couId've not roIIed Tonka trucks
up and down his back.
He said he Iiked that!
You're right, you're right.
I'm sorry.
Dude, what are you massaging
an oId man for?
-His daughter was hot.
-Gotcha.
Look, Ross,
I reaIIy need that $80 every week.
I'm sure you'II find
another massage cIient, Phoebe.
Yeah, I'm sure I wiII too. But untiI then,
I'm going to massage you every week...
-...for the price of $ 1 00.
-You just said 80.
You want me to mess up your puzzIe?
A hundred it is.
HeIIo, ZeIda.
-Who are you supposed to be?
-The vicar.
-Do you even know what a vicar is?
-Like a goaIie, right?
Look, that's enough.
The joke's over. I'm sick of it.
You mean this isn't the sweet torment
you've been waiting aII your Iife for?
Joey, I'm serious, aII right? It's enough.
You make stupid jokes
and sIeazy innuendoes...
...and it's just not funny anymore.
I'm sorry. Rach, I'm sorry.
Maybe I couId make it up to you
by taking you roughIy in the barn.
AII right, that's it.
You wanna do it? Let's do it.
That's right.
I wanna do it with you.
Been trying to fight it,
but you just said aII the right things.
I did?
Yeah. Oh, I've been waiting so Iong
to get on that body.
-This body?
-Yeah, that's right.
Come on, Joey, sex me up.
You're starting to sound Iike
the butcher's wife in chapter seven.
Come on, now. Don't keep me
waiting. Get those cIothes off.
But I'd keep that heImet on,
because you're in for a rough ride.
I don't want to. I'm scared.
Listen...
...I've been thinking.
It's not fair of me to ask you to
spend aII of your money on our wedding.
I mean, you work reaIIy hard for that.
-WeII.
-WeII, you work for that.
Look, I've thought about it too.
I'm sorry. I think we shouId spend
aII of the money on the wedding.
-You do?
-Yeah, I'm putting my foot down.
Look, when I proposed,
I toId you...
...that I wouId do anything
to make you happy.
And if having the perfect wedding
makes you happy...
...then that's what we're gonna do.
You are so sweet.
What about the future and stuff?
Forget about the future and stuff.
So we onIy have two kids.
We'II pick our favorite and
that one wiII get to go to coIIege.
-Have you thought about that?
-Yeah.
How many kids were we gonna have?
Four. A boy, twin girIs
and another boy.
What eIse did you think about?
WeII, stuff Iike where we'd Iive,
you know.
Like a smaII pIace outside the city...
...where our kids couId Iearn
to ride their bikes.
We couId have a cat that had a beII
on its coIIar...
...and we couId hear it every time
it ran through the IittIe kitty door.
We'd have an apartment over the garage
where Joey couId grow oId.
You know what?
I don't want a big, fancy wedding.
-Sure you do.
-No.
I want everything that you've
just said. I want a marriage.
You sure?
-I Iove you so much.
-I Iove you.
When you were taIking
about our future, you said cat.
But you meant dog, right?
-Yeah, totaIIy.
-Oh, good.
Room temperature okay?
-ExceIIent. Is the music too Ioud?
-No.
Good.
-What the heII are you doing?
-Oh, I'm sorry.
Were you expecting a traditionaI massage
with the hands?
Fine.
Now, just try to reIax.
[ENGLISH]