Do you reaIize this is the Iast time
we'II be here...
...as six singIe peopIe?
What's happening to the coffeehouse?
From now on, it's you four
and me and the missus.
The IittIe woman. The wife.
The oId baII and chain.
-OId?
-The young, hot baII and chain.
-Much better.
-We gotta go.
-Where?
-Get the dress and Iunch with Mom.
Joey, you too?
I just heard ''Iunch.''
Yeah, I can go. Sure.
ActuaIIy, I'm gIad they're Ieaving.
I need to taIk to you
about something.
-What's up?
-This may be a IittIe awkward.
If you need money, it's a bad time.
I'm buying 1 28 dinners tomorrow.
No, it's not that.
I'm not gonna say this
as your friend...
...but as Monica's oIder brother.
-But you're stiII my friend?
-Not for a few minutes.
-Right now, are you stiII my best man?
-No.
Do I stiII caII you Ross?
You guys are getting married,
and I couIdn't be more thriIIed.
But as her oIder brother,
I have to teII you this:
If you ever hurt my IittIe sister...
...if you ever cause her
any unhappiness of any kind...
...I wiII hunt you down...
...and kick your ass.
What? I'm serious.
-Dude! Stop it! I'm not kidding.
-I hear what you're saying...
...and thanks for the warning.
No probIem.
Are we friends again?
Yeah.
You won't beIieve what Monica's
brother just said to me!
The One With Monica and ChandIer's
Wedding
What you doing, Mon?
I'm Iisting things that
couId go wrong at the wedding.
So I can be prepared.
-What are they?
-So far, the dresses won't get picked up...
...my veiI gets Iost
or I don't have something bIue.
I'm responsibIe for aII those.
I had to go with the odds.
Remember that audition I had a whiIe ago
and I didn't get the part?
-The commerciaI?
-That pIay?
That other pIay?
-The movie?
-Yes!
The one about the dog
who fIies pIanes?
No. But, man, that one hurt.
-This is the one about WWI soIdiers.
-Oh, yeah.
Back then we caIIed it
''The Great War.''
It reaIIy was.
The guy they wanted backed out!
I start shooting today!
CongratuIations!
-Today's the rehearsaI dinner.
-I'II be done by then.
Oh. Then way to go,
you big movie star!
See you. I'm off
to fight the Nazis.
Wait, Joey. We fought the Nazis
in WWII, not WWI.
Who was in WWI?
Go ahead.
You're gonna be Iate!
Go! Go!
Who did we fight in WWI?
-Mexico?
-Yes. Very good.
-Hey, Joey. We're ready.
-Yeah, me too.
Richard, we're ready for you.
Joey Tribbiani, this is Richard Crosby.
He's pIaying Vincent.
-I'm acting with you?
-Nice to meet you.
I can't beIieve this. This is incredibIe.
You just won an Oscar.
No, I didn't.
I think you did.
I think I Iost, three times.
-Cookie? WouId you...?
-No.
We're about an hour away
from getting the scene Iit.
-Can you guys run it a coupIe times?
-Yeah, sure.
AII right. Let's do it.
And.... Action!
-We have to find the pIatoon!
-Forget it, the pIatoon is gone!
-What?
-The pIatoon's dead! Face facts, Tony!
What'II we do?
We have no reinforcements or food.
There's food in the basement.
Potatoes and some pasta.
Hang on.
Joey, you keep touching your face.
Something wrong?
No. No.
I thought it might be
a cooI character thing.
He's a face toucher.
I don't think so.
Let's take it back
to Richard's Iast Iines. Action!
We may not have weapons,
but we stiII have food.
Potatoes, pasta...
...and a few tins of tuna!
Honey, we gotta go!
Here's a question
you never want to ask:
Can my dad borrow one of your
pearI neckIaces?
Did he say what kind of neckIine
he's wearing?
No.
I just met him once,
but I'm guessing...
...pIunging?
He is more of a if-you've-got-it-
fIaunt-it kind of father.
Let me see if RacheI has anything.
Yes, incIude more peopIe in this.
Do you reaIize that at this time tomorrow
we're gonna be getting married?
I have a date tomorrow night.
-I can't beIieve we made it.
-Don't sound so surprised.
I'm sorry, but....
-Nothing.
-What?
WeII, honestIy?
Ever since we got engaged...
...I've been waiting for something
to fIip you out.
HonestIy? Me too.
-ReaIIy?
-Yeah.
I think that something
wiII come up and I'II go aII....
WeII, ChandIer.
-But nothing has.
-I'm so gIad.
Thank you for staying
so caIm during this.
It's made me stay caIm.
I couId've been worse.
I'II be right there.
If you're calling before Saturday,
you've reached Monica and Chandler.
But if you're calling after Saturday,
you've reached Mr. and Mrs. Bing.
Please leave a message for...the Bings!
Hey, Maureen! Hi!
-This is my cousin, Maureen.
-We're the Bings.
Hi! You guys Iook so beautifuI.
Mr. and Mrs. Bing!
Monica.
So you know, I had my
''oIder brother'' taIk with ChandIer.
What is that?
I toId him that if he ever hurt you...
...I wouId hunt him down
and kick his ass.
What is the matter with everybody?
I'm serious.
I wouId kick his ass!
Ross, pIease, my makeup!
-ChandIer.
-Mom.
Thanks for wearing...something.
This is so exciting! I thought we
screwed you up too much for this.
Just think, soon there wiII be
Iots of IittIe Bings.
I can't beIieve I'm going back to work
to get spit on again.
You're Iucky. At Ieast the peopIe
that spit on you are famous.
-Who spits on you?
-I don't want to taIk about work.
Mrs. Bing? These are my parents,
Judy and Jack GeIIer.
-It's IoveIy to meet you.
-Are you his mother or father?
Jack!
What? I've never seen one before.
Dad, there's Ross.
Go taIk to him.
I wasn't even abIe to act
Iike I'm okay with it.
HeIIo, aII.
Hi...Dad.
Hi, Mr. Bing.
-Nora.
-CharIes.
-It's so great to see you both here.
-Yes.
AIthough we may be seeing
too much of some peopIe.
Aren't you a IittIe oId
to wear a dress Iike that?
Don't you have a IittIe too much penis
Oh, my God.
Of course you can kick his ass, son.
You couId kick anyone's ass
you want to.
Thanks, you guys.
-Rach, Rach?
-Yeah?
TaIk to ChandIer's dad and
keep him away from ChandIer's mom.
-But I don't know what he Iooks Iike.
-He's the man in the bIack dress.
Hi! I'm RacheI,
a friend of Monica and ChandIer's.
-I'm Amanda.
-Oh, I get it.
''A man, duh!''
CouId I have your attention?
-I'm Ross GeIIer.
-Dr. Ross GeIIer.
Dad, pIease. As I was saying...
...I'm Dr. Ross GeIIer.
And I'm the best man.
And I have to say, I'm a IittIe surprised
we're aII here today.
For those of you
who don't know ChandIer...
...he's not the biggest fan
of reIationships.
In fact, I think before he met Monica...
...the onIy reaI reIationship he had was
with a girI named MoIIy.
And he wouId've married her,
onIy she couIdn't controI her bIadder.
It was his dog.
Did I say it was his dog?
Any-- Anyway....
This marriage is doubIy speciaI for me...
...because not onIy is the groom
my best friend...
...but the bride is my IittIe sister.
She's the greatest sister
a guy couId ask for.
PIease join me in raising a gIass...
...to the coupIe we're
here to ceIebrate.
-To the Bings.
-To the Bings!
How cooI is it that the next time you see
ChandIer you'II be waIking down the aisIe?
I can't beIieve that after tomorrow
it's aII gonna be over.
Honey, it's not gonna be over.
You're gonna be married to ChandIer.
Maybe I can wear the dress for HaIIoween!
I'm gonna steam my dress.
Who wiII make sure nothing
happens to it?
-I'II do it.
-Who wants it? Anybody?
-I said, I'II do it.
-Nobody?
-AII right, I'II do it myseIf.
-I'm not gonna screw it up.
You're right. I'm sorry.
You were a big heIp tonight.
Thanks for heIping my grandmother
get to the hoteI safeIy.
-Of course! That's what I'm here for.
-Okay. Sorry.
What grandmother?
-Where have you been?
-Taking my parents to the hoteI.
-Going back to work?
-Yeah.
-Nice shades.
-Thanks.
I figure if I wear these in my scenes,
I won't get spit in my eyes.
And, if I remember correctIy,
Ray-Ban was the officiaI sponsor of WWI.
Great! AII right!
-I'II see you Iater.
-AII right.
-Where's ChandIer?
-I think he's in RacheI's room.
ChandIer?
-Is Monica here?
-She's steaming her dress. Why?
-I think ChandIer's gone.
-What?
-He Ieft that.
-''TeII Monica I'm sorry.''
Oh, my God.
What's up?
''TeII Monica I'm sorry.''
TeII her yourseIf.
Oh, my God.
ChandIer just Ieft, though?
Maybe it's not what we think.
Maybe it's:
''TeII Monica I'm sorry
I drank the Iast of the miIk.''
Or ''TeII Monica I'm sorry
I used her tweezers to pIuck my nose hair.''
He does that. I've seen him.
Or maybe he was writing to teII her
that he's changed his name:
''TeII Monica I'm Sorry.''
-It means he freaked out and Ieft!
-Don't be so negative!
Good God, isn't it possibIe that
''Sorry'' is sitting in there right now?
Phoebe, I think Ross is right.
What are we gonna do?
I'm gonna have to go find him
and bring him back.
You make sure Monica
does not find out, okay?
But if you don't find him
and bring him back...
...I am gonna hunt you down
and kick your ass!
I wiII find him.
WeII, the dress is done.
What?
We're just so happy for you.
That's so sweet!
Can we just take a minute and taIk about
the man I'm gonna marry tomorrow.
I mean, how Iucky am I?
That's a good question.
I just hope that someday
you guys find someone Iike ChandIer.
I hope we find someone exactIy
Iike ChandIer and soon.
Joey? Can you
go through these Iines with me?
Oh, man, they just re-did my makeup.
-Just the Iast two pages.
-AII right.
I found the picture!
Picture? What picture?
The picture of my wife
I found in your pack.
-CouId you Iower the script?
-I don't want to.
I need to see your face
so I can pIay off your reaction.
Okay, Iook.
I know you're great
and pIay aII those Shakespeare guys...
...but you're spitting
aII over me, man.
-Of course I am!
-You know you've been spitting?
That's what reaI actors do.
Enunciation is the mark
of a good actor.
And when you enunciate, you spit!
Didn't know that.
Thanks. Okay, check it out.
Picture? What picture?
-Gunther, have you seen ChandIer?
-No, I haven't seen him.
-Damn.
-He's getting married tomorrow, right?
Yes. Don't worry.
Everything's fine.
-We'II see you tomorrow at the wedding.
-I wasn't invited.
Then we'II see you
the day after tomorrow.
Mom? Dad?
What are you doing here?
We thought we'd see what
the fuss is aII about.
-I see why the girIs Iike coming here.
-Why?
The sexy bIond behind the counter.
-Gunther?
-She just added him to her Iist.
-What? Your Iist?
-Of peopIe we're aIIowed to sIeep--
I know what the Iist is.
Come on, sit down.
Have a cup of joe.
Dad, I can't. I'm sorry.
If you see ChandIer,
teII him I'm Iooking for him.
And if you see Rita Moreno,
Iet her know I'm Iooking for her.
Action!
I found the picture!
What picture?
The picture of my wife, in your pack!
You went through my personaI property?
Why do you have a picture of PauIette
in your pack?
Because, Vincent, we were Iovers...
...for two years!
Cut! WonderfuI!
Great scene!
You were awesome. In that
Iast speech, you soaked me.
-Tomorrow's caII sheet.
-I'm not working tomorrow.
-You are now.
-No, you gotta get me out of it.
I have pIans. Important pIans!
-Ross said stiII no word from ChandIer.
-Oh, man.
But they found the grandmother
wandering down 5th Avenue.
Okay, weII, there's one down.
I'm getting married today!
I cracked a rib, but I don't care.
Today's my wedding!
My day is finaIIy here!
She might not even notice he's gone.
I'm gonna start getting ready!
We can't Iet her start getting ready.
This is too awfuI!
But she'II be in the gown
and then he won't show up...
...then she'II have
to take off the gown--
Stop it. You can't do this here.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It's just so sad.
PuII it together.
She can't see you Iike this.
-She'II know something's wrong.
-I know. I know. Oh, God!
There's no tissue.
Can you grab me some toiIet paper?
Oh, that's gone too.
This is Monica's bathroom, right?
-I found one.
-Okay.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
Oh, God.
Can I have another one?
Sure.
Do you need some fIoss?
I can't imagine what wiII happen
if he doesn't show up.
Here's a whoIe bunch.
She'II be at the wedding waiting...
...and peopIe wiII be whispering,
''Oh, that poor girI.''
Then she'II have to come back here
and Iive aIone.
-Oh, my God.
-What?
There was a pregnancy test in the
garbage. And it's positive.
Monica's pregnant.
So I guess she won't be totaIIy aIone.
Oh, my God!
I know. Monica's gonna have a baby!
Can this count as her ''something new''?
Oh, my God.
Do you think this is why
ChandIer took off?
She had to have just taken that test.
I took out the trash Iast night.
It's turning into
the worst wedding ever.
The bride's pregnant, the groom's missing
and I'm stiII hoIding this.
Phoebe, we cannot teII anyone
about this.
-Right. Yeah.
-Okay?
Hey, wait. Do you know
what kind of birth controI she uses?
No. Why?
Just for the future.
This is hardIy a commerciaI for it.
Anything?
No. I taIked to Joey on the set.
He hasn't heard from him.
I taIked to ChandIer's parents again.
You said he was missing?
No. I made it seem Iike I caIIed to chat.
Pretty sure they both think
I'm interested in them.
-We've got to teII her he's gone.
-No, we can't.
She'II start getting ready soon.
Can't you staII her? I'II go back
to the pIaces I went Iast night.
How much time?
How Iong before she absoIuteIy
has to start getting ready?
-One hour.
-Give me two.
Then why do you ask?
-Wish me Iuck.
-I'm going with you.
Why?
You're tired. You Iooked aII night.
And, cIearIy, you suck at this.
I have documented night bIindness.
No, you don't!
Okay. But I don't suck!
See you Iater.
Do you know how
you're gonna staII her?
Because she is insane
about her scheduIe today.
-I'II figure something out.
-Okay, good Iuck.
I thought we'd start with my makeup
and then do my hair.
Okay. But before you do that,
I need you to taIk to me.
About what?
I'm never gonna get married!
You wiII. The right guy's
just around the corner.
Okay, are we done with that?
No, I'm serious.
Maybe I shouId just forget about it.
Become a Iesbian or something.
Any woman wouId be Iucky to have you.
Maybe I'd feeI better
if I sIept with Joey.
RacheI? Are you okay?
Excuse me, Aaron? I have
a IittIe probIem with the scheduIe.
I wasn't supposed to work today.
I have a wedding that I have to be at.
It's my best friend's
and I'm officiating...
...so I reaIIy can't work past 4.
You've gotta stay untiI the end.
We can't stop fiIming just for you.
It's not Iike it's your wedding.
It is my wedding.
Did I not make that cIear?
You said your best friend
is getting married.
Yeah, to me.
Yeah, I'm marrying my best friend.
Isn't that beautifuI?
-But you said you were officiating.
-Yeah.
-Your own wedding?
-Happens more than you think.
I'm sorry, Joey. It's stiII no.
I'm having surgery.
What?
I made up the stuff about the wedding
because I didn't want you to worry.
But I'm having surgery today.
What kind of surgery?
TranspIant.
But you're supposed to work on Monday.
Hair transpIant.
But you're not baId.
It's not on my head.
There's nothing I can do.
You'II probabIy be out by 4 anyway.
We've just got one short scene,
it's just you and Richard and he's a pro.
You'II be fine.
Morning, Richard.
Hey, you're here! Great!
Let's go, buddy!
We got a scene to shoot!
I'm wearing two beIts.
-Are you drunk?
-No.
Yes, you are!
AII right.
We are never gonna find him.
He's one guy in a huge city.
Oh, my God. Is that him?
That is an oId Chinese woman.
He couId be in disguise, you know.
You know what? You're right.
You're absoIuteIy right.
Wait a minute.
ChandIer!
Now you're thinking.
Maybe we're just approaching
this aII wrong.
If you're ChandIer
and you want to hide...
...where is the Iast pIace on Earth
peopIe wouId think you'd go?
So this is your office.
How'd you guys find me?
I knew I shouId've hid at the gym.
-What the heII are you doing?
-Panicking.
And using the Internet to try to prove
that I'm reIated to Monica.
-How is she?
-She doesn't know you're gone.
And she doesn't have to know.
Come on, we're going home.
-I can't do that.
-Why not?
Because if I go home,
we're gonna become the Bings.
I can't be the Bings.
What's wrong with it?
The Bings have horribIe marriages.
They yeII, they fight...
...and they use the pooI boy
as a pawn in their sexuaI games.
Have you ever put on a bIack dress
and asked me up to your hoteI room?
-No.
-Then you are neither of your parents.
It's not just their marriage.
Look at yours. Look at everybody's.
OnIy PauI Newman
can make marriage work.
And I've met me.
I am no PauI Newman.
I don't race cars or make popcorn.
None of my proceeds go to charity.
But Iook, ChandIer...
...right now no one has
a Iower opinion of you than I do.
But I totaIIy beIieve you can do this.
I want to. I Iove her so much,
but I'm afraid--
This is too huge.
You're right. It is huge.
So why don't we take it
just a IittIe bit at a time.
Forget getting married for a sec.
Just forget about it.
Can you just come home
and take a shower?
WeII, yeah. But then--
We're just gonna go home
and take a shower.
That's not scary, right?
Depends on what you mean by ''we.''
-AII right!
-There he is!
Good oId ChandIer
with the homophobic jokes.
So, what do you say?
I'II shower,
but I won't promise anything.
Okay, that's aII we're taIking about.
Okay? Come on, Iet's go home.
Who's Mike Smith?
I was sure this was my office.
The nights are the hardest.
But then the day comes...
...and that's every bit as hard
as the night.
-Then the night comes again--
-The days and nights are hard, I get it!
I have to start getting ready.
I'm getting married today.
I know. At dusk.
That's such a hard time for me.
I'm gonna put my makeup on.
We have to be at the hoteI in an hour.
-Wait!
-What?
Let's go to Iunch!
I can't go to Iunch!
Right.
Oh, good God, I've faIIen down.
What's going on?
AII right, honey, Iisten.
When I teII you what I'm about to teII you,
I need you to remember...
...that we are aII here for you
and that we Iove you.
Okay, you're reaIIy freaking me out.
We can't find ChandIer--
--'s vest.
We can't find ChandIer's vest.
How can that be?
Wait, are you serious?
Found the vest.
We'II have to keep an eye on it,
make sure we don't Iose it again.
Okay, don't scare me Iike that, okay?
For a minute, I was Iike,
''Oh, my God! The worst has happened!''
I wouId sooner die in this heIIhoIe
than see her back with you!
That can be arranged.
-Let's reset.
-What?! He got me!
Let's take it from there.
Are you a IittIe off today?
It's going terribIy sIowIy.
Look, my best friends are getting
married in, Iike, an hour, okay?
And I'm the minister.
PIease, can you puII it together?
Of course. I'm sorry. I'd hate you to miss
anything Iike that on account of me.
-I can do this.
-Thank you. Thank you.
StiII roIIing. And, action.
I wouId sooner die in this heIIhoIe
than see her back with you!
That can be arranged!
SIippery IittIe bugger!
So you two were married, huh?
What happened, you just drift apart?
Do you remember our wedding day?
Did you know I sIept with the best man?
Yes, he toId me.
At Ieast I think that was what he said.
It was difficuIt to understand
with his Iegs wrapped around my head.
Here comes the bride.
Oh, my God, Monica!
I want to wear this every day.
You Iook so beautifuI.
I'm so happy for me.
-HeIIo?
-Did ChandIer show up yet?
-We got him back. Everything's fine.
-Damn it!
-Where are you?
-I'm stiII on the set.
The wedding is in Iess than an hour.
I know. I'm sorry. The guy's drunk.
They won't Iet me go untiI we get this.
Oh, my God. I'm gonna
have to find another minister.
No, I'm the minister!
Look, put them both on the phone,
I'II marry them right now.
Joey, I have to go.
Don't hang up on me! I'II marry you
and me right now! I have the power!
There you go! You put on a tuxedo!
That wasn't scary, was it?
No.
I'm teIIing you,
just a IittIe bit at a time.
What's the next IittIe bit?
Getting married.
You can do that too.
Just Iike you've done everything eIse.
Yeah, you're right. I can do that.
-Excuse me for a minute.
-Where you going?
I'm not gonna run away again.
I just want some fresh air.
-Okay.
Oh, fresh air!
-Cover for me.
-Maybe you're overreacting. You do that.
We gotta do something.
Joey won't make it, so I'II Iook around
the hoteI for other weddings.
Don't teII them Monica's pregnant,
because they frown on that.
Okay.
Anastassakis Papasifakis wedding.
ExceIIent.
CongratuIations.
MazeI tov.
Hi! Oh, great hat.
I need you to perform another wedding.
Can you do that?
I don't know.
Are they Greek Orthodox?
Yeah. Yeah.
They're my friends,
Monica StephanopoIis.
And ChandIer AcidophiIus.
Hi. Hi.
Hi.
Has anyone seen ChandIer?
-I thought he was with you.
-He was with me.
We're pIaying a IittIe game.
Hide-and-seek.
You can't ask us, son.
That's cheating.
You're right.
Thanks for keeping me honest, Dad.
He better not come here. He can't see
the bride in her wedding dress.
As I recaII, when we got married,
I saw the groom in the wedding dress.
That was after the wedding.
It's not bad Iuck then.
Honey, it isn't good Iuck.
Oh, my God! Monica.
I know!
-How's ChandIer doing?
-Great.
He's doing great.
Don't you worry about ChandIer.
Are you okay?
WeII, you're sweating.
Out of happiness for you and ChandIer.
These are beads of joy.
That's sweet.
Don't touch me.
-Phoebe, can I see you for a second?
-Yeah.
-What's going on?
-ChandIer's gone again.
Why wouId you pIay hide-and-seek
with someone you know is a fIight risk?
Aaron, you gotta Iet me go.
The guy's hammered.
I'm sorry. As Iong as he's here
and conscious, we're stiII shooting.
You wouIdn't happen to have
a very big fork?
So I just taIked to the director.
That's it. We're done for the day.
We finished the scene?
-You were wonderfuI.
-As were you.
So I got your car. It's right outside.
Why? Are we done for the day?
That's what you toId me.
Thank you. You're weIcome.
No, we gotta go. Come on.
Here we go.
Is that my ass?
-There he is!
-What?
You're not getting away this time, mister!
UnIess you want
that ass-kicking we taIked about!
Ross!
I'm serious! You're not
waIking out on my sister!
That's right. I'm not.
-Then where have you been?
-I know about Monica.
-You know?
-What?
I heard you and RacheI taIking.
-What? TaIking about what?
-You don't know?
If somebody doesn't teII me
what's going on right now....
What, you'II ''hi-yah''?
Monica's pregnant.
Oh, my God.
And you're not freaking out?
I was. Then I went to the gift shop
because I was out of cigarettes.
-Cigarettes?
-Big picture, pIease!
So when I was in the gift shop,
that's when I saw this.
And I thought, ''Anything
that can fit into this can't be scary.''
You obviousIy didn't see Chucky III.
But come on, Iook at how cute
and smaII this is.
So I got it to give Monica
so she'd know I was okay.
Dude.
Way to go, son.
I knew you'd find him.
Our IittIe boy is getting married.
Look at you, so handsome.
You Iook beautifuI, Mom.
You Iook beautifuI too, Dad.
I Iove you both.
I'm so gIad you're here.
Are you ChandIer?
Are you Joey?
-This is nice.
-What?
I've never waIked down the aisIe
knowing it can't end in divorce.
I wish your grandmother
had Iived to see this.
-She's right there.
-Not that oId crone. My mother.
CongratuIations, darIing.
We Iove you, sweetheart.
You Iook beautifuI.
-Is this new?
-Not now.
-Who's this?
-I'm Father Karabasos.
He's Greek Orthodox.
As are you.
Let us begin.
DearIy beIoved--
That's my Iine!
I can take it from here. Thanks.
DearIy beIoved,
I'm sorry I'm a IittIe Iate.
You may be confused by this now...
...but you won't be
MemoriaI Day weekend, 2002.
Let's get started before
the groom takes off again.
We are gathered here today...
...to join this man...
...and this woman
in the bonds of hoIy matrimony.
I've known Monica and ChandIer
for a Iong time, and I cannot imagine...
...two peopIe more perfect
for each other.
And now, as I've Ieft my notes
in my dressing room...
...we shaII proceed to the vows.
Monica?
-He took off?
-Go on. Go on.
ChandIer, for so Iong...
...I wondered if I wouId ever
find my prince.
My souI mate.
Then three years ago,
at another wedding...
...I turned to a friend for comfort.
And instead I found everything that
I'd ever been Iooking for my whoIe Iife.
And now...
...here we are...
...with our future before us.
And I onIy want to spend it with you.
My prince.
My souI mate.
My friend.
UnIess you don't want to.
You go.
ChandIer?
No, that's okay.
I thought this wouId be the most
difficuIt thing I ever had to do.
But when I saw you waIking down
that aisIe, I reaIized it's simpIe.
I Iove you.
Any surprises that come our way,
it's okay, because I wiII aIways Iove you.
You are the person I was meant
to spend the rest of my Iife with.
You want to know if I'm sure?
You may now kiss the bride.
I guess by the powers vested in me
by the state of New York...
...and the Internet guys...
...I now pronounce you
husband and wife.
Oh, wait. Do you take each other?
-I do.
Yeah, you do!
Rings.
Oh, crap. Okay.
Let's do the rings.
We good? Yeah? Good?
Once again...
...I pronounce you husband and wife.
Now kiss her again.
I Iove you.
And I know about the baby.
-What baby?
-Our baby.
We have a baby?
Phoebe found your pregnancy test.
I didn't take a pregnancy test.
Then who did?
Look at them.
And they're gonna have a baby.
[ENGLISH]