[ALL WHISTLING THEME FROM
THE BRIDGE ON THE RIVER KWAl]
Rach, we're running low
on résumés over here.
Do you really want a job
with Popular Mechanics?
Well, if you're gonna work for mechanics,
those are the ones to work for.
Hey, look, you guys.
I'm going for anything here, okay?
I can't be a waitress anymore. I mean it.
I'm sick of the lousy tips.
I'm sick of being called "Excuse Me."
Rach, did you proofread these?
Uh, yeah. Why?
Uh, nothing. I'm sure they'll be impressed
with your excellent "compuper" skills.
Oh, my God!
Oh, do you think it's on all of them?
Oh, no, I'm sure the Xerox machine
caught a few.
- Hey, guys.
BOTH: Hey.
Hey. Hi, ladies.
Uh, can I get you anything?
- Did you bring the mail?
- Lots of responses.
Really? Sure we have scones left.
Okay, read them to me.
"Dear Miss Green: Thank you
for your inquiry. However..."
- We have apple cinnamon...
- Okay, "Dear Miss Green"...
Yeah. Yeah, yeah. No.
- Wow.
- What?
Your Visa bill is huge.
Give me that.
You know, I can't believe you.
Linda is so great.
- Why won't you go out with her again?
- I don't know.
Is this still about her whole...
..."The Flintstones could
have really happened" thing?
It's not just that.
It's just, I want someone
who does something for me...
...you know,
who gets my heart pounding...
...who makes me, uh...
Little play things with yarn?
What?
Could you want her more?
Who?
Who? Dee, the sarcastic sister
from What's Happening!!
Who?
Look, I am totally, totally over her, okay?
- I just... Hi.
- Hi. Coffee?
- No, we're fine.
- Okay.
[CHANDLER & ROSS LAUGH]
Shut up.
We're not saying anything.
- What?
- Uh, Joey cried last night.
Thank you.
We were playing poker, right?
There was chocolate on the three.
It looked like an eight, all right?
Oh, God, you should've seen him.
"Read them and weep."
And then he did.
Well, now, how come you guys
have never played poker with us?
Yeah, what is that?
Like some kind of guy thing?
Like some kind of sexist guy thing?
Like, it's poker, so only guys can play?
No. Women are welcome to play.
Oh, okay, so then what is it?
Some kind of, you know, like,
some kind of, you know, like...
All right, what is it?
There just don't happen
to be any women in our game.
Yeah, we just don't happen to know any
women that know how to play poker.
Oh, please. That is such a lame excuse.
I mean, it's a typical guy response.
Excuse me, do any of you
know how to play?
[IN UNISON]
No.
But you could teach us.
[IN UNISON]
No.
Okay, so now we draw cards.
So I wouldn't need any, right?
Because I have a straight.
- Oh, good for you.
- Congratulations.
[MICROWAVE BEEPING]
Okay, Pheebs, how many do you want?
Okay, I just need two.
The 10 of spades and the six of clubs.
No, uh, Pheebs, you can't do that.
I have the 10 of spades.
Here, you want it?
Thanks.
Uh, no, see, uh, you can't do that.
No, no. That's okay. I don't need them.
I'm going for fours.
Oh, you're...
All right, here we go.
We've got salmon roulettes
and assorted crudités.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Monica, what are you doing?
This is a poker game. You can't serve food
with more than one syllable.
It's got to be like chips
or dip or pretz...
Okay, so at this point, the dealer...
You know what? We got it. We got it.
Let's play for real. High stakes. Big bucks.
All right, now, you sure?
Phoebe just threw away two jacks...
...because they didn't look happy.
But I'm ready. So just deal.
Okay, all right, last minute lesson.
Last minute lesson. Joey.
Three...
...eight.
Eight, three. All right. Here we go.
Damn it, damn it, damn it.
I see. So then, um, you were lying.
- About what?
- About how good your cards were.
Heh. I was bluffing.
Aha. And what is "bluffing"?
Is it not another word for lying?
Okay, sorry to break up this party...
...but I've got résumés to fax
before work tomorrow.
ROSS: Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Rach, we've got to settle.
Settle what?
The Jamestown colony of Virginia.
You see, King George
is giving us the land, so...
The game, Rachel. The game.
You owe us money for the game.
Oh, right.
You know what, guys? It's their first time.
Why don't we forget about the money?
Hell, no. We'll pay.
Okay, Monica,
I had another answer all ready.
And you know what?
- We want a rematch.
- Well, that's fine with me.
Could use the money.
So, basically, you get your ya-yas
by taking money from all of your friends.
- Yeah.
- Yes, and I get my ya-yas from lkea.
You have to put them together yourself,
but they cost a little less.
Look, Rachel, this is poker.
I play to win, all right?
In order for me to win,
other people have to lose.
So if you're gonna play poker with me,
don't expect me to be a nice guy.
Okay, because once those cards
are dealt...
Yeah?
I'm not a nice guy.
All right, boys. Let's eat.
Ah, did you get that from
the "I Love Rachel" pizzeria?
- You still on that?
- Come on.
What was with that whole
Black Bart speech?
"When I play poker, I'm not a nice guy".
You're way off, pal.
No, I don't think so.
See, Ross, because I think you love her.
Uh, no.
See, I might have had feelings for her
at one time. Not anymore.
I just... Marcel.
Where are you going with that disk?
You are not putting that on again.
Marcel... Okay. If you press that button,
you are in very, very big trouble.
[THE TOKENS' "LION SLEEPS TONIGHT"
PLAYING ON SPEAKERS]
You believe what a jerk Ross was being?
Yeah, I know.
He can get really competitive.
[LAUGHS]
What?
Oh. "Hello, Kettle, this is Monica.
You're black."
Please.
I am not as bad as Ross.
Oh, I beg to differ.
The Pictionary incident?
That was not an incident.
I was gesturing and the plate
slipped out of my hand.
Oh.
- Oh! I got an interview. I got an interview.
- You're kidding. Where? Where?
- Saks Fifth Avenue.
- Oh, Rachel.
Oh, it's like the mother ship
is calling you home.
- Well, what's the job?
- Assistant buyer.
Oh! I would be shopping...
...for a living.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Okay, look. That's Aunt Iris.
This woman has been playing poker
since she was 5.
You've gotta listen
to every word she says.
- Hi.
- Is Tony Randall dead?
- Oh, why?
- I don't think so.
Well, he may be now
because I think I hit him with my car.
- My God. Really?
- No, that's bluffing. Lesson number one.
Let me tell you something.
Everything you hear
at a poker game is pure crap.
- Nice earrings.
- Thank you.
Girls, sit down.
- Um, Aunt Iris, this is Phoebe, and Rachel...
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Listen, I am parked at a meter.
Let's do it.
[THE TOKENS' "LION SLEEPS TONIGHT"
PLAYING ON SPEAKERS]
Ross, could we please, please,
listen to anything else?
All right.
[MUSIC STOPS]
I'm gonna pay for that tonight.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
- Hi.
- Hey.
Guess what, guess what, guess what.
Uh, okay. The fifth dentist caved,
and now they're all recommending Trident?
No, the interview.
She loved me. She absolutely loved me.
We talked for, like, two and a half hours.
We have the same taste in clothes.
Oh, I went to camp with her cousin.
And, oh, the job is perfect.
I can do this. I can do this well.
GROUP:
That's great.
God. And she told the funniest story.
Okay, great,
you'll tell us and we'll laugh.
Let's play poker.
All right, listen, we talked about it...
...and if you don't want to play,
we completely understand.
Yes, yes. We can play some other game.
Like, I don't know...
...Pictionary?
Very funny. Very funny.
I think we'd like to give poker another try.
Shall we, ladies?
BOTH:
Yes, I think we should.
Rach, do you want me to shuffle those?
No, no. That's okay. You know what?
I'm gonna give it a go.
ROSS: All right.
- All right.
So Pheebs owes 7.50.
Monica, you owe $10.
And, Rachel, you owe 15 big ones.
Thanks for teaching us
"Crossed-eyed Mary."
You guys, we gotta play that other way.
All right, here's my 7.50, but I think
you should know that this money is cursed.
- What?
- Oh, I cursed it.
So now bad things will happen
to he who spends it.
That's all right, I'll take it.
Bad things happen to me anyway.
This way, I can break them up
with a movie.
So that just leaves the big
Green poker machine, who owes 15.
Hmm, oh, it's so typical:
"Ooh, I'm a man. Ooh, I have a penis.
Ooh, I have to win money
to exert my power over women."
You know what? This is not over.
We will play you again.
And we will win and you will lose.
And you will beg and we will laugh.
And we will take
every last dime you have.
And you will hate yourselves forever.
Hmm. Kind of stepped on
my point there, Mon.
So you gals wanna hand over
your money now?
That way, we don't have to go
through the formality of actually playing.
No, that's fine. We'll see
who has the last laugh there, monkey boy.
Okay, are we done with the chitchat?
Are we ready to play serious poker?
Hey, you guys, look. The one-eyed jack
follows me wherever I go.
Right, okay. Serious poker.
MONICA:
Excuse me. Where are you going?
Uh, to the bathroom.
Do you wanna go to the bathroom
or do you wanna play poker?
I wanna go to the bathroom.
- All right, well, I'm gonna order a pizza.
- Oh, no, no, no.
I'm waiting to hear from that job.
And the store closes at 9,
so you can eat then.
That's fine. I'll just have a Tic Tac
to hold me over.
All right. Cincinnati. No blinds.
Everybody ante.
Yes.
Or no.
ROSS:
All right.
Your money's mine, Green.
Your fly's open, Geller.
You guys, you know what I just realized?
"Joker" is "poker" with a "J."
Coincidence?
Hey, that's "jo-incidence" with a "C."
[CHUCKLES]
- Uh, Phoebe. Phoebe...
- Yeah, I'm out.
I'm in.
Me too.
Me too. All right. What do you got?
Well, you better hop out of the shower,
because I got a flush.
Well, well, well.
Hop back in, bucko,
because I got four sixes.
I got four sixes. I won. I actually won.
Oh, my God. You know what?
I think I'm gonna make a little Ross pile.
I think that one was Ross'.
And I think, oh, that one was Ross'.
[SINGSONG] Well, I have got your money.
And you'll never see it.
And your fly's still open.
I made you look.
PHOEBE: I'm in.
RACHEL: I couldn't be inner.
PHOEBE:
Monica? Monica, in or out?
I hate this game.
Okay, Joey, your bet.
I fold, like a cheap hooker
who got hit in the stomach...
...by a fat guy with sores on his face.
Oh, I'm out.
- Ross?
- Oh, I'm very in.
- Chandler?
- Couldn't be more out.
Me too. Rachel?
Um, I will see you and I'll raise you.
What do you say?
You wanna waste another buck?
No, not this time.
- So, what did you have?
- I'm not telling.
- Come on, show them to me.
- No.
- Show them to me. Let me see.
- Get your hands out of there.
You know, I've had dates like this.
Boy, you really can't stand to lose,
can you?
Your whole face is getting red.
Little veins popping out of your temple.
Plus that shirt doesn't really
match those pants.
First of all, I'm not losing.
[PHONE RINGS]
- Just deal.
- Hello? Rachel Green.
[MIMICKING RACHEL]
Excuse me.
It's about the job.
Barbara, hi. How are you?
Uh-huh?
No, I understand.
Yeah, oh, come on. No, I'm fine.
Don't be silly.
Yeah. Oh, but you know,
if anything else opens up, please...
Hello?
[SCOFFS]
Hmm.
Sorry, Rach.
Yeah, you know,
there's gonna be lots of other stuff.
Yeah. Okay.
Where were we? Oh. Okay.
Five card draw. Uh, jacks are better.
Nothing wild, everybody ante.
Look, Rach, we don't have to do this.
Yes, we do.
- All right. Check.
- Check.
I'm in for 50 cents.
- Call.
- I'm in.
I see your 50 cents...
...and I raise you...
...$5.
I thought, uh, it was a 50-cent limit.
Well, I just lost a job,
and I'd like to raise the bet 5 bucks.
Does anybody have a problem with that?
- Not at all.
- No, no.
[MONICA CLEARS THROAT]
Loser?
No, I fold.
What do you mean, you fold?
Hey, come on, what is this?
I thought that, "Once the cards
are dealt, I'm not a nice guy."
I mean, what? Were you just full of it?
[CLEARS THROAT]
I'm in.
- How many you want?
- One.
Dealer takes two.
- What do you bet?
- I bet $2.
Okay.
See your 2...
...and I raise you...
...20.
- Wow.
I see your 20...
...raise you 25.
See your 25...
...and, uh, Monica, get my purse.
Rachel, there's nothing in it.
Okay, then get me your purse.
Okay. Here you go. Good luck.
Thank you.
I saw your 25 and I raise you...
...7.
- Teen.
[GROANS]
Joey, I'm a little shy.
That's okay, Ross. You can ask me.
- What do you need? What do you need?
- Fifteen.
- All right, here's 10.
- Here, I got 5, I got 5.
- Thank you.
- Good luck.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Okay, I am calling your 17.
What do you got?
Full house.
You got me.
GROUP:
Oh!
[MONICA & PHOEBE HUMMING]
[JOEY & CHANDLER GROANING]
[SHOUTS]
- That's a tough hand to beat.
- I thought we had them.
Well, when you don't have the cards,
you don't have the cards, you know?
But look how happy she is.
ROSS: Airmail.
CHANDLER: Airplane. Airport.
Airport '75. Airport '77. Airport '79.
[TIMER DINGS]
RACHEL:
Time's up.
Bye Bye Birdie.
That's a bird?
That's a bird.
RACHEL:
Okay, okay, it's my turn.
Go.
Uh, Bean. Bean.
- The Unbearable Lightness of Being.
- Yes!
[ALL SHOUTING]
That you get?
[English - US - SDH]