[PHONE RINGS]
Hello?
CHANDLER [OVER PHONE]: It's me. I know
you can't stand to be in the same room.
I just thought I'd try and apologize
over the phone...
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello?
CHANDLER [OVER PHONE]: Look, I never
should've kissed your girlfriend, and I'm...
[PHONE RINGS]
Stop calling!
CHANDLER [OVER PHONE]:
Hey, hey, hey. This is 92.3 WXRK K-Rock...
...calling with our $1000 daily challenge.
All right.
What is the name of...
...your roommate who is very, very sorry
and would do anything...?
Ugh, turkey.
Ugh, giving thanks. Ugh.
Look, everyone,
it's the spirit of Thanksgiving.
Are things with Joey any better?
They couldn't be worse.
I spent eight hours calling him...
...trying to get him to talk to me.
Oh, wow. Eight hours.
So you could probably really use one
of those plug-in telephone headsets, huh?
Should we all expect Christmas gifts
that can be stolen from your office?
You shouldn't.
Speaking of Christmas...
...since Monica and I are starting
a new business and have like no money...
...this year maybe we could do Secret Santa
and then we each only buy one gift.
And there's the added mystery of,
you know, who gets who.
Who gets "whom."
I don't know why I do that.
[CROWD CHEERING ON TV]
Oh, I'm gonna take a nap.
Turkey makes me sleepy.
We haven't eaten yet.
I know, but all that work you're doing
to get it ready, and I just...
Hey, did either of you pick Rachel
for your Secret Santa?
- Because I wanna trade for her.
- I picked her. Oh, thank God, you want her.
Ooh.
Wow, why do you wanna get rid of her
so badly?
Because she exchanges
every gift she gets.
It's, like, impossible
to get her something she likes.
Come on, let's trade.
That's not true.
I got her that backpack and she loved it.
I remember how much she was crying
the day that big dog ran off with...
There was no big dog.
This sucks, because I already got her
this briefcase and I had "R.G." put on it.
- Her initials.
- Oh.
Maybe you can give it to somebody else.
Oh. Like Ross Geller.
Oh, you know what, though?
It's a girlie briefcase.
Who cares? He works in a museum.
Hey, what time is it?
The big game's about to start.
Ross and Joey aren't here.
You can watch the parade if you want.
Thanks.
MONICA:
What is wrong with this freezer? Ow! Ow!
- God, what happened?
- Oh, my God, ice just got in my eye.
People are trying to sleep in here.
Monica got ice in her eye and it hurts.
- Open it up. Let me see.
- Oh, I can't. It really kills.
Well, maybe you should put
some ice on it.
- Ooh, it looks bad.
- Maybe we should take you to a doctor.
No, my eye doctor is Richard.
I can't go to him
when I don't have a boyfriend.
He's really picky about his patients.
Okay, you've gotta go.
What's his office number?
Oh, like I remember his office number.
Speed dial 7.
Hi, yeah, I'm calling on behalf
of Monica Geller's eye, and...
Is Richard Burke in today?
He's out of town.
Does she wanna see the on-call doctor?
- Yes.
- Yes. She's very excited about that.
It's so cool.
Till Monica gets back, it's like I'm head chef
and I get to make all the decisions.
Hey, hey, I thought she told you
to follow the recipe exactly.
Okay, get out of my kitchen.
All right, okay. I think I'm making
some progress with Joey.
When I went into the apartment,
he went to his bedroom...
...but he only slammed the door once.
I mean, yeah,
he gave me the finger while doing it.
All right, I gotta call my mom and ask her
a left-handed cooking question.
So listen,
I picked Monica for Secret Santa...
...but I'm getting her something
for Hanukkah.
You wanna switch?
Oh, you know what?
I was trying to trade for, uh, ahem, well, you.
[CHUCKLES]
Really? Wow, that's so nice.
What are you gonna get me?
I don't know, R.G. I was thinking
something girlie for your office.
Yeah. Well, maybe Phoebe
will switch with me.
Then you're gonna get stuck with Rachel,
and she exchanges every gift she ever gets.
Oh, that's not true.
I got her lots of stuff she never took back.
Like?
Like that gold necklace
I got her last year.
When was the last time
you saw her wear it?
Well, she wore it all Christmas day
and then, uh...
Big dog?
- Hey.
What are you doing?
Sending back this stuff Chandler bought
out of guilt.
- Everything? Even the TV?
- No, I'm gonna put that in my room.
Listen, Joey.
I know what he did was wrong.
But don't you think
you could hear the guy out?
When you and Rachel were together...
...if Chandler had kissed her,
would you hear him out?
That's a good point.
So how long you gonna punish him?
Five years.
You've sentenced him?
Hey, don't do the crime
if you can't do the time.
- But, Joey, the guy's your best friend.
- No, was my best friend.
I don't know why
you're pushing for him so hard.
With him out of the way as my best friend,
there's a spot open.
- Who, me?
- Yeah.
Wow. I'm honored.
You know what I'm gonna do
as my first act as your best friend?
I'm gonna get you to talk to Chandler.
All right.
Oh, but if you weren't my best friend...
Ah.
Oh, my God. Is it really that bad?
I walk in the room,
and he won't even talk to me.
He just mumbles something in Italian.
And I know he only knows
the bad words.
Hey, Gunther, have you seen Chandler?
I thought you were Chandler.
But, um, one of you is over there.
Oh.
Hey, Joe.
[SPEAKS IN ITALIAN]
I'll be right with you, okay?
Thanks for coming in.
Oh, my God.
How cute is the on-call doctor?
Oh. So cute that I'm thinking
about jamming this pen in my eye.
[MONICA CHUCKLES]
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Dr. Burke will see you now.
Oh, no, no, no, not Dr. Burke.
Dr. Burke's out of town.
The on-call doctor will see me now.
Dr. Richard Burke is out.
Dr. Timothy Burke, his son,
will see you now.
Ready?
Hey, I'm sorry. That...
- Where you going?
- My folks'.
Oh. Uh...
When you coming back?
I don't know.
I might stay there for a few days
while I look for an apartment.
What?
Yeah, you know, at first I thought
we could talk about this, work it out.
But seeing you two together, I don't...
Hey, look, what do you want me to say?
Do you want me to say I'll stop seeing her?
It's not about her. Okay?
But seeing you two together
just reminds me of what you did.
And I don't wanna live with someone
who doesn't know what it is to be a friend.
- So I'll see you.
- Hey, look, I know what it is to be a friend.
- I just... I screwed up.
- Yeah, you did.
And that's why I'm leaving.
[CHICK & DUCK SQUAWKING]
Look, if you're not gonna stay for me,
then at least stay for them.
Okay? They have had a very difficult year,
what with the robbery and all.
When that guy was robbing us...
...and I was locked in the entertainment unit
for six hours...
...do you know what I was doing?
I was thinking about how I let you down.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
If I'd have known what kind of friend you
were gonna be, I wouldn't have worried.
- See you around.
- All right, wait, come on.
Just wait one second.
There has to be something that I can do.
If we still had that unit...
...I would get in there for six hours
and think about how I let you down.
What?
We got a box.
I remember the last time I saw you.
It was the morning I left for college.
You were just standing
outside the Dairy Queen.
Heh. Just probably waiting for it to open.
Gotta tell you, you look great now.
- You look great too.
- You're an excellent patient.
So how does it look?
You've got a little scratch on your cornea.
You're gonna have to wear a patch.
Like a pirate?
If that helps you.
Ahem. So how long have you been working
with your dad?
Come on, one of us had to mention him.
I moved back here a couple months ago.
Ah.
- Big family dinner tonight?
- Uh...
MONICA:
No way.
I was gonna have Thanksgiving
at my girlfriend's.
- Oh.
- But we broke up.
Oh?
She wasn't ready
for a serious commitment.
Oh.
[IN PIRATE VOICE] So you made her
walk the plank, aye, matey?
You're not wearing the patch yet.
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
I know.
- He's coming here for Thanksgiving?
- I know. It's sick.
- Why is it sick?
- Because it's Richard's son.
It's like inviting a Greek tragedy
over for dinner.
I mean, come on,
Phoebe, you understand, don't you?
Yeah, I could see where I'd be
your best shot, but no.
- Sorry, honey. I think it's twisted.
- Yeah.
- What's twisted?
- Oh. Me going out with Richard's son.
Ew.
Ew, ew, ew.
CHANDLER:
It sounds like a really bad idea to me.
Is he okay in there?
He's fine.
You know, if things work out
between you and Richard's son...
...you'll be able to tell your kids
that you slept with their grandfather.
[CHUCKLES]
Fine, judge all you want to.
But married a lesbian, left a man at the altar,
fell in love with a gay ice dancer...
...threw a girl's wooden leg in the fire,
live in a box.
So, now, ahem,
what exactly is the point of the box?
Chandler?
CHANDLER:
The meaning of the box is threefold.
One, it gives me the time
to think about what I did.
Two, it proves how much I care
about my friendship with Joey.
And three...
...it hurts.
- Oh, hey, hey, uh...
- Hmm?
Remember that necklace
I gave you last year?
Can I see it?
Why?
I just wanna check something.
Okay.
Now we'll see.
CHANDLER:
Air hole! Air hole!
Here it is. I love it. I wear it all the time.
The necklace I got you was gold.
This is silver.
Huh.
Well, maybe, it, uh...
...it changed.
Oh, my God. You actually exchanged it.
Isn't it better that I exchange it
for something that I enjoy...
...and I can get a lot of use out of?
What did you get?
Credit.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
I'll get it, I'll get it, I'll get it.
- Hi, Tim.
- Hi.
Hi. Thank you. Come meet my friends.
- This is Phoebe.
- Hi, nice to meet you.
- And Joey.
- Hey.
TIM: Joey.
MONICA: My brother, Ross.
- Hey.
MONICA: And Rachel.
- Hi.
CHANDLER: Ahem.
[MONICA CLEARS THROAT]
- That's Chandler.
CHANDLER: How do you do?
- What's...?
- Um, well, he's, um...
He's doing some thinking.
MAN [ON TV]:
He's got it.
- Yes!
- Yeah!
CHANDLER: What happened?
- You kissed my girlfriend.
Ooh, I like those sunglasses.
"Like them" like them...
...or "I'd like to get store credit
for that amount" like them?
[SPEAKS IN ITALIAN]
All right, everybody. This turkey is ready.
- Where can I wash up?
MONICA: Here.
Let me show you.
The towels are hanging next to the sink.
And you can use the fancy soap. Ha, ha.
Thank you.
Fancy soap?
I thought we were saving that for the Pope.
See? He's nice, right?
Do you really wanna be in a relationship
where you can actually use the phrase...
..."That's not how your dad
used to do it"?
Wow, everything looks great.
Where should I sit?
Saved you a seat.
Sick, sick, sick.
[KNOCKING]
Oh, I'll get it.
CHANDLER:
Gotcha.
[CHANDLER LAUGHS]
That doesn't sound like thinking to me.
CHANDLER: Sorry.
- I don't think you should be talking at all.
I think you got too much thinking to do
to be talking and making jokes.
CHANDLER:
Okay, okay, you got it.
- Ross, could you pass me the yams?
- Sure.
Oh, and Joey's got the mashed potatoes
if you want to exchange them.
Will you stop?
What is the matter with you?
Heh, heh. We've got company.
There's nothing the matter with me.
See, I'm not completely devoid
of sentiment.
See, I have feelings.
Okay, fine.
CHANDLER: You can't tell, but I'm trying
to break the tension by mooning you guys.
All right, look.
If this is just a big joke to you,
then forget about it, all right?
This means something to me.
If it doesn't mean anything to you,
then get out of there.
Otherwise, you're just an idiot in a box.
CHANDLER: You're right. I'm sorry.
This means a lot to me.
I want you to be my friend again.
I swear I won't say another word tonight.
- So you're gonna take this thing seriously?
CHANDLER: Absolutely.
That sounds like another word to me.
Are you gonna take this seriously?
Okay.
Don't say that I have no sentiment.
This is a movie stub from our first date.
This is an eggshell from the first time
you made me breakfast in bed.
This is from the museum,
the first time we...
...were together.
Okay, maybe I exchange gifts sometimes,
but I keep the things that matter.
I don't know what to say. I'm sorry.
Though...
...you're not supposed to take these.
It's like a million years old.
We actually...
We have people looking for that.
Oh, this always happens.
Here, let me, um...
Thank you.
You have very beautiful...
...eye.
My friends all think this is weird.
I thought it was gonna be weird.
I almost called to cancel, but it really isn't.
I know. I mean, it's like me and your dad,
that's a totally separate thing.
Oh, I totally agree.
I mean, we're just two people
who find each other...
...very attractive.
Right?
- What?
- Nothing, nothing.
No, no, really. Oh, was that not okay?
No, no, no, that was good.
That was, uh... That was a good kiss.
- Oh, my God. It didn't remind you of my...?
- Oh, don't say it.
- But it did, didn't it?
- Yes!
Oh, man.
I know.
[BOTH SHUDDER]
[MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY ON TV]
[SHUDDERS]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
I got it.
[JOEY CLEARS THROAT]
Oh.
- Hey.
- I want you to know how sorry I am...
- It's okay.
Chandler's the one I'm mad at, so...
Well, I'm still sorry.
- Is he here?
- In the box.
Chandler?
Oh, he can't talk right now.
Why not? What's going on?
He's trying to show Joey
how much he means to him.
- By being in a box?
- Joey had reasons.
They were threefold.
Oh. Well, uh...
...you not being able to talk
might actually make this easier.
Listen, um...
Listen.
I don't wanna be someone
who comes between two best friends.
I just... I can't stand seeing
what this is doing to you guys.
And I don't wanna be the cause of that.
So I don't think
we can see each other anymore.
I'm gonna go to my mom's in Chicago.
I'm gonna stay there for a while.
I think this could have been something
really amazing.
But, you know,
this is probably for the best.
You know?
I'm gonna miss you.
Goodbye, Chandler.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
Open the box.
RACHEL: What?
- He can still catch her.
Hey, come on. Get out of there.
Get out of there.
- So...?
- Yeah, we're gonna be fine. Get out.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
You did some real good thinking in there.
I mean, this is...
[MUMBLES INDISTINCTLY]
Now go. You could still catch her.
And merry Christmas
from your Secret Santa.
All right, who got Chandler?
Because I need to trade.
Oh, he sees her.
Aw, and he's catching up to her.
Oh, she sees him.
- Oh, they're hugging.
RACHEL: Aw.
He's taking her purse.
Uh, that's not them.
I'm gonna go call the police.
- Oh, there they are.
- Where?
- Ah!
- Oh.
Aw.
All right, get a room.
[English - US - SDH]