Hello!
What's this?
Oh, right!
It's that girl's phone number.
There it is.
Just a phone number...
...a really hot girl gave me.
No big deal. I mean,
it is her home phone number but...
Whoa!
Whoops! Heh. Almost lost this baby!
The lovely Amanda gives me her number,
and I go and drop it.
[GASPING]
[SNEEZES]
Thank you.
- Rachel?
- Yeah?
- When's your birthday?
- May 5th. Why?
I'm making a list of birthdays.
- Mine's December...
- Yeah, whatever.
CHANDLER:
Oh! She's pretty!
Pretty, uh, pretty girl. The pretty...
She's pretty.
- Go ask her out.
- Ha, ha.
- What's the worst that could happen?
- I could die.
Yeah, it's tough being single.
That's why I'm so glad I found Amanda.
Ross, you guys went out once.
You took your kids to Chuck E. Cheese,
and you didn't even kiss her.
I tell people secrets.
It makes them like me.
Hey.
[PHEOBE SNEEZES
AND GROUP GROANS]
Phoebe.
You're sick.
You shouldn't play. Go home.
[IN CONGESTED VOICE]
But I'm unemployed.
My music is all I really have now.
Well, music and making my own shoes.
Pretty, huh?
All right, I'll do it.
I'll go get shot down.
Any advice?
Just be yourself...
...but not too much.
Wish me luck.
Good luck!
Wish it!
Hi. I was just sitting over there and...
Uh, my name's Chandler.
Did I say that?
No, you didn't. Hi, I'm Kathy.
- Kathy with a K or a C?
- With a K.
Hey!
Wow, you are really good at this!
I'm out on a limb here!
I'm sorry. You're right.
But I should tell you
I'm waiting for a date.
And there he is now!
- Hey!
- Hey! Hey!
- I see you guys already met.
- Yeah.
I was trying to demonstrate...
...how I could get my
very large feet...
...into my even bigger mouth.
Didn't I tell you?
Always showing off.
[CHUCKLES]
Before I start, I want to say
that I have a cold.
So if I sneeze during a song,
it's not on purpose.
Oh! Except the last verse of
"Pepper People."
[CLEARS THROAT]
[SINGING IN CONGESTED VOICE]
Smelly cat, smelly cat
What are they feeding you?
This chick sounds good.
Smelly cat
Gunther, be a good little boy
and bring me a whiskey.
- Hi.
At 2:30 a.m., I didn't expect
to fight over the remote.
Sorry, there's this Ernie Kovacs
thing I wanted to watch.
That's why I got up too.
You're kidding? I love him!
Sorry about this afternoon.
If I'd known, I wouldn't have...
Oh, please. Heh.
Joey tells me you two met
in acting class.
We were partners.
Joey picked three scenes for us.
- All of them had us making out.
- Ha-ha-ha.
That's good, because he used to
make me rehearse with him.
[CHUCKLES]
- Oh, oh, oh!
- Is it on?
No, but this wonder broom is amazing!
Hey!
Oh, my God!
Oh! It's on!
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHICK CHIRPS]
Here we go, little fella.
What about the duck?
- The duck can swim.
- Of course.
[SINGING IN CONGESTED VOICE]
My sticky shoes
My sticky, sticky shoes
Why you stick on me?
Baby
Thanks for the lights, honey.
Way to go!
Your cold makes you sound great.
It's fun.
God, I love how sexy I am!
[COUGHING]
Kath, we should get going.
We're going to buy hamsters.
GROUP: Aw.
- I love them.
No, it's not like that.
I work for a medical researcher.
- Have fun.
- Okay.
It's nice that
the medical community...
...is trying to help sick hamsters.
- You know, I like Kathy.
- Yeah?
Me too!
She's so cool and pretty.
She is.
She's smart and funny.
We were up all last night talking.
She said the funniest thing about...
What?
You love her.
No, I don't.
Yes, you do. Chandler loves Kathy.
- Come on, just lay off him.
- Thank you.
He's a little sensitive right now
because he's so in love!
All right.
[GROUP MOANS AND KISSES]
MONICA:
Ooh, Kathy!
Kathy, I love you!
[MOANS AND KISSES]
I need to write some depressing stuff
for my new bluesy voice.
But nothing sad has
ever happened to me.
How about your mom dying?
Or living on the streets
when you were 14?
Uh-huh.
I could write about when
my hair did that woo-hoo thing.
- Hey.
MONICA & PHOEBE: Hey.
I'm going over to Amanda's tonight.
- Rachel's not here.
- Oh.
How's it going with her?
Great, actually. I'm thinking
tonight may be the night.
The kids will play together,
and when they're asleep...
...Amanda and I break
open a bottle of wine...
...do a little playing ourselves.
Hi, guys! This is Josh.
Josh, these are my friends.
And that's Ross.
- Hi, Josh.
PHOEBE: Hi.
Dudes.
You played in college?
Aw, I still do.
Next year, I hope to make varsity.
Didn't you play soccer
in high school?
No, wait. You organized their
game schedules on your Commodore 64.
It's getting late. I got to get
to the game, so I'll... head.
I'll miss you.
Dope!
Wow! Cute one.
- Very cute.
- I know. Isn't he great?
So nice to finally be in a
fun relationship, you know?
There's nothing boring about him.
I bet he's never set foot
in a museum.
Maybe he'll get to go soon.
Like on a class trip or something.
You know what else is
great about him?
Ugh, what's the word for an adult...
...who has no dinosaur toys
in their bedroom?
Oh...
What was that?
Monica knows.
It's this dumb thing Ross made up
to fool our parents.
It's a way of giving the finger
without actually giving it.
I cried the night you made that up.
It was the first time I realized
I was cooler than my big brother.
I'm going to go get ready...
...for my date tonight...
...so I'll just head.
I should go too.
I'm playing in one hour.
Hey...
[CLEARS THROAT]
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
You guys should come hear me. Ooh!
Hear me. Ooh!
[SINGING]
My sticky shoes
Ew! Ew!
I lost my sexy phlegm!
ROSS: Hi.
- Hi. Hi, Ben.
- You look great!
- Thanks.
Yeah, okay...
Hey, Tommy!
I'm so glad you could come tonight.
Oh, no. It's my pleasure.
My cell phone number
is on the counter.
Help yourself to the fridge.
I appreciate this.
I've been trying to date...
...this guy for a month.
I...
Uh, I'd appreciate it
if you'd drink your wine...
...after the kids are asleep.
Oh, uh...
Thanks for this. I hope I can do
the same for you sometime.
Who wants to make
some long-distance calls?
Kathy! Kathy!
Hi, Kathy! Kathy!
[CAR HORN HONKS]
Kathy!
Fetch! Fetch it!
Kathy! Kathy!
[MUFFLED SHOUTING]
Kathy!
Hey. Chandler, what are you doing here?
I just wanted to say, "hey!"
- Hey!
- Okay.
You're making it sound
worse than it was.
Her date tipped me $10!
What are you doing?
I want to be sexy again,
so I'm trying to catch a cold.
Should be easy.
They're pretty common.
MONICA:
You'll catch pneumonia!
You were right.
I'm in love with Joey's girlfriend.
- What?
- Are you serious?
How's that possible?
You barely know her.
I don't know. I just...
I can't get her out of my head.
I'm a very bad person.
I'm a very, very bad person.
I'm a horrible person.
"No, you're not.
We still love you, Chandler!"
[SNEEZES]
Phoebe, I think I caught your cold.
You mean you stole it!
Don't cover your mouth
when you do that!
[CHUCKLING]
JOEY:
Hey.
We were just talking about you.
Really?
The time you got drunk
and fell asleep...
...with your head in the toilet.
[LAUGHING]
Right in there!
Ninety-nine...
...a hundred.
Ready or not, here I come!
Let's go over the concept
one more time.
- Hey!
You want to get some dinner
with me and Kathy tonight?
Oh, um... You know what? I already ate.
- It's 4:30.
- I had a big meal on Monday.
So that'll get me
straight through the week.
I see what's going on here.
- You do?
- Yeah.
You don't like Kathy.
You got me.
You've been avoiding her
since we started dating.
I made an effort to like Janice.
Now you make an effort to like Kathy
by going out with us. Right?
- Yeah, right.
- Good. And hey, my treat.
Because you're not eating, right?
Right.
Ross isn't here.
Oh. Stop it!
I'll see you at the party?
Beer's fear, man! 24/7!
Yeah!
I am so going to marry that guy.
- Ugh!
- What?
I think he's stealing from me.
Why?
Because he's stealing from me!
- Hi, it's me.
RACHEL: Hi.
And soup.
I saw Josh. He looked yummy
in your leather jacket.
[GRUNTS]
I don't eat chicken,
so it's just noodle soup.
There's no chicken in the broth,
so it's really noodle water.
MONICA: Thank you so much.
- Sure.
What are you doing?
I need your germs.
I want my cold back.
I miss my sexy voice.
Sorry, Phoebe.
It's okay.
- How's the soup?
- Mm.
[GROANS]
[UPBEAT ROCK MUSIC
PLAYING ON STEREO]
Oh! Check it out!
You can see that girl's underwear.
- Is she great, or what?
- Ha, ha.
Huh? What do you think?
She's not really my type.
Not your type? She's gorgeous.
You know what it is?
The fishnet stockings.
Whenever I see a girl in those,
it reminds me of...
...my father in fishnet stockings.
Understanding a little more of
why you're single.
I have a friend you'd like.
We could double date.
No, thanks.
I've got some ugly friends
who are available too.
I'm going to grab a beer.
I'll be right back.
- What was that?
- What?
Kathy's being really nice
and you walked away.
What do you want from me?
I want you to like her.
If that's too damn difficult,
then at least you could pretend.
I am pretending.
Then do it better.
What do you say, I go tell her
how much I like her?
I could tell her
I've been thinking of her.
I haven't stopped thinking
of her since we met.
I'm so over-the-top,
want-to-slit-my-own-throat...
...in love with her,
that every minute...
...I can't believe my own damn bad luck
that you met her first!
That's pretty good.
But you might want
to tone it down a little.
Hey. Uh, Amanda just dropped me off.
That's one of the things
I love about her.
She's old enough to drive.
You're not going
to Mom and Dad's tonight?
No. Sorry.
Where's Amanda?
Get me some cough drops.
I'm thinking you could bring her...
...and go to your old room
and not make out.
Cough drop, please?
At least she's not
going out with me...
...to get into R-rated movies.
[MONICA COUGHING]
Why don't you marry her?
Wait, you can't! I forgot.
She's not a lesbian.
Amanda and I...
You have nothing!
You're not even going out!
You're her babysitter.
You have a 12-year-old girl's job!
[LAUGHING]
Oh, that is so sad.
What are you laughing at,
Miss My-keg-sucking-boyfriend...
...- is-stealing-from me?
[GRUNTING]
So he stole a few bucks.
Big deal!
He got me something with it.
That's mine!
Would you both please
start acting like adults?
And give me my cough drops!
- Fine.
- Sorry.
- Here.
- Thank you.
At least I made $10 in my relationship.
You know...
[SINGING]
Parading goats are parading
Parading down the street
Leaving little treats
Does it even work
without my sexy voice?
I like it.
[SNEEZES]
- Gunther, kiss me.
- What?
Do it, Deputy! Do something!
[JOEY & KATHY GIGGLING]
[TELEVISION VOLUME INCREASES]
Hey!
[VOLUME DECREASES]
We aren't exactly sleeping in here,
but do you mind?
Can I sleep on your couch?
[SNAPPING FINGERS]
[SINGING IN FRENCH ACCENT]
And I'm still waiting
For my papier-mâché man
Thank you, my babies.
- Rachel?
RACHEL: Yeah?
Did you hear what happened
between me and Phoebe?
- No.
- We kissed.
I didn't initiate it,
but I also didn't stop it.
I've been feeling guilty.
Okay
So, um...
...are we cool?
Okay.
I knew you would understand.
[English - US - SDH]