HeIIo.
I Iove my new job!
-Honey, you're screaming.
-You bet your ass I am!
I just had the best first day ever!
The kitchen?
Twice as big as AIIessandro's.
Oh, that's great.
And cIean? Not just heaIth
department-cIean, Monica-cIean!
Awesome.
Oh, and the peopIe are so nice.
There's this one guy, Jeffrey,
he's the maître d' .
ChandIer, you wiII Iove him!
He is without a doubt
the funniest guy I have ever met!
-This is nice.
-I know.
-You need both hands for that?
-Yeah, I kind of do.
WeII, how's this?
Are you sure that's sweet enough?
Look at you two hoIding hands.
Is this getting serious?
Have you not taIked about it yet?
Am I making you uncomfortabIe?
If you were bigger you'd hit me.
I'm sorry.
It's obviousIy way too earIy
for us to be having that conversation.
-Is it?
-Maybe not. Is it?
When I got divorced...
...I didn't think I'd feeI this way about
someone for a reaIIy Iong time.
Then again, I didn't think I'd meet
someone Iike you. And....
This may be crazy-soon,
but I want you to have this.
No, not.... That's gum.
Oh, five bucks!
I Iove it when that happens, you know?
-You don't know it's there--
-I know. Keep digging.
Sorry.
It's a key.
To be honest, I think I'd prefer
the five doIIars.
-It's to my apartment.
-Wow!
Big step for Phoebe and Mike.
I don't want you to feeI Iike you
have to give me your key....
-No, I want to.
-Thank God.
Wow. I was starting to think
I'd never meet someone that...
...I wanted to do this with.
Here you go.
-This is cooI.
-It reaIIy is.
I know it. It is amazing.
These IittIe things open doors!
So I don't go back to work
for another four weeks...
...but we wouId Iike our nanny
to start right away...
...so that Emma couId get
a chance to know her.
I think that's reaIIy smart.
The easier we can make the
transition for her the better.
That's great. Great.
-So do you have any questions for us?
-Not reaIIy.
AII right. WeII, thank you
so much for coming.
-Thank you.
-It was reaIIy nice to meet you.
-We wiII caII you.
-Oh, you know, wait.
I do have one question.
Do you guys do random drug testing?
Boy, we hadn't reaIIy thought of that.
That's cooI. But if you do,
I'm gonna need three days' notice.
Okey-dokey!
We're never gonna find a nanny.
Come on, Rach. We wiII. I promise.
We have more interviews.
Worse comes to worst, we can aIways
reconsider the first one we met with.
-What, the bIond with no bra?
-She was bIond?
Just a sec.
Okay, this one's name is Sandy.
She's got a degree in
EarIy ChiIdhood Education.
She worked for her Iast famiIy
for three years.
Hi. I'm Sandy.
And she's a IittIe mannish.
Oh, my God! David!
-Is this a bad time?
-No, it's a great time! Come in!
Wow! Hi!
Oh, my gosh! What are you doing here?
Are you back from Minsk?
Just for a coupIe of days.
I'm here to expIain to the peopIe
who gave us our grant...
...why it's a positive thing that
we've spent aII their money...
...and accompIished nothing.
Who cares? It got you here.
It got me to New York.
Then I got in a cab at the airport...
...and the guy said, ''Where to?''
I just gave him your address.
I didn't even think about it.
Where's your Iuggage?
Damn it.
AII right, I'II caII the cab company.
We can caII them Iater.
Can you just stand there for a moment?
Boy.
There's an oId Russian expression
that goes:
RoughIy transIated, that means:
''This thing that I'm Iooking at: Wow.''
Thank you.
You shouId see me when--
ActuaIIy, no, I Iook pretty good.
Are you kidding?
You know, when you don't see
someone for a Iong time...
...you buiId them up in your head,
you start thinking:
''Come on, don't be crazy,
nobody's that beautifuI.''
But, weII, you are.
WeII, so are you seeing anyone?
No.
I'm just the worst person ever!
How can I not teII David
that I'm seeing Mike?
Maybe he didn't give you a chance.
He said, ''Are you seeing someone?''
and I said, ''No.''
WeII, that wouId've been your window.
I mean, I don't know.
I was Iooking in his eyes...
...and I was just thinking,
''Oh, my God, it's David. David's here.''
He's so irresistibIe.
-ReaIIy? The scientist guy?
-ReaIIy? ChandIer?
Continue.
Then it gets worse...
...because I toId him
I wouId see him tomorrow night.
-Phoebe!
-I know! EviI!
I Iike Mike so much, you know?
It's just going reaIIy weII. Oh, my God!
Isn't it ironic that David
wouId show up...
...on the same day that
you and Mike exchange keys?
Yeah. You know, and given
my IifeIong search for irony...
...you can imagine how happy I am!
-What are you gonna do?
-I mean, I guess I just have to...
...teII David that nothing
can happen between us.
UnIess I don't.
You know, compIicated moraI situation?
-No right, no wrong?
-You have to teII David.
I knew I shouId've had this conversation
with Joey.
Funniest guy she's ever met.
I'm funny, right?
What do you know? You're a door.
You just Iike knock-knock jokes.
Save it for inside.
So OkIahoma's a crazy pIace. You know,
they caII it the Sooner State.
FrankIy, I'd sooner be in any other state!
And what's with OkIahoma
having a panhandIe?
Can aII states have stuff Iike that?
Hey, yeah, I'm from the waistband
of Wyoming.
But when I was 7,
we headed over to the crotch.
Was your cabin pressurized?
And don't get me started on the way
the peopIe from TuIsa taIk.
Okay.
What's with the word ''y'aII''? You know,
just two words just pushed together?
Are we aII aIIowed to do that?
Because if so, I say why stop there?
You know, your new poodIe
couId be your noodIe.
And fried chicken couId be fricken.
Waiter? Waiter, excuse me,
I'II have the fricken!
See, that's funny with the fricken, right?
No, it just reminds me of something
this guy did today at work.
I toId you about that funny guy, Jeffrey,
right?
Yeah, he came up.
WeII, he did this bit.
You probabIy had to be there...
...but it was Liza MinneIIi Iocked
in our freezer eating a raw chicken.
-Were you there?
-No, but it sounds fricken funny.
I reaIIy understand how hard it's gotta be
to Ieave your chiId with another person.
I mean, it's Iike Ieaving behind
a piece of your heart.
Sandy, that's exactIy what it is.
Are you gay?
I'm sorry, that's our Ross.
He's just Mr. Shoot Straight From The Hip.
It's okay. I get that a Iot doing what I do.
But I am straight. I'm engaged, actuaIIy.
-Her name's DeIia.
-That's pretty.
So you're just, Iike,
a guy who's a nanny.
I reaIize how it's a bit unorthodox
for some peopIe.
But I reaIIy beIieve the most satisfying
thing you can do with your Iife...
...is take care of a chiId.
Okay.
Like at my Iast job.
I met DanieI when he was
3 weeks oId.
And I got to watch him grow
into this awesome person.
When I Ieft, I said, ''I'II see you soon.''
And he said to me, ''Skadandy?''
That was his name for me.
''I'II see you every day right in....''
-It's okay.
-Yeah, kids say aII kinds of crap.
Oh, God, she must need
her diaper changed.
-I can take care of that, if you want.
-That wouId be great.
Just so you know, these dinosaur toys
aren't reaIIy age-appropriate.
They're mine.
AIso not age-appropriate.
I Iove him, I Iove him, I Iove him!
Come on. Rach, he's a guy!
So what? He's smart. He's quaIified.
Give me one good reason
we shouIdn't try him out.
Because it's weird!
Why?
Wow, I never Iooked at it that way.
What kind of a job is that for a man?
A nanny?
I mean, it's Iike if a woman
wanted to be--
Yes?
King?
I hope you don't mind. I used
some of my homemade Iotion on Emma.
It's a mixture of caIenduIa and
honey cream. It'II dry that rash right up.
PIus, it keeps the hands young.
Yes! Sandy, you're hired!
That's great!
I'm sorry.
It's just such an emotionaI thing
when you're weIcomed into a new famiIy.
Oh, God. Come here.
You gotta be at Ieast bi.
I need you to set me up for a joke.
When Monica's around,
ask me about fire trucks.
I don't know, ChandIer. I'm not
so good with remembering Iines.
Thank God your IiveIihood
doesn't depend on it.
I know, right?
Why are we doing this?
Monica says that her maître d' is
the funniest guy she's ever met.
-SeriousIy? She actuaIIy said that?
-Yes. Am I crazy to be this upset?
-No! Being funny's your thing!
-Yeah!
Without that, you just got
''Iame with women'' !
Hi! There you are.
Fire trucks!
-Hi.
I brought you this from Minsk.
You're not gonna beIief this.
This is Iemon-fIavored vodka.
Yeah, we actuaIIy have this here.
I traded four pairs of Levi's for that.
Thanks anyway.
Wow. You Iook even more beautifuI
than you did yesterday.
In fact, I'm going to kiss you now.
-Wait, wait.
-I can't get away with stuff Iike that.
It sounded sexy in my head, so I....
No, no, it's not that.
Remember when you asked me if
I was seeing someone and I said no?
WeII, I am. His name's Mike.
-I shouId've toId you.
-No.
WeII, yeah.
I'm sorry. I wanted to teII you,
but then I just got Iost in your eyes...
...and I just forgot aII about....
-Mike?
-Right, yes.
-I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
-WeII, it's okay. I understand.
WeII, are you happy with this guy?
-I am happy.
-Damn it.
I'm sorry. I don't mean that.
I want you to be happy.
But onIy with me. No, that's not fair.
Who cares. Leave him.
I don't mean that. Yes, I do.
I'm sorry.
I think I shouId probabIy go.
But, David, I just want you to know that,
you know...
...teIIing you this is one of the
hardest things I've ever had to do.
WeII, just so you know...
...hearing it wasn't exactIy
a VIadnik carnivaI, either.
-Can we at Ieast hug goodbye?
-Of course. Yeah.
You know, and a kiss on the cheek
wouIdn't be totaIIy inappropriate.
-No. No.
-I mean....
-In Minsk?
-Yeah?
It's two on each cheek...
-...and one on the Iips.
-WeII, if that's what they do in Minsk.
In New York, it's--
Oh, boy.
Is everything aII right?
Oh, yeah. No, it's fine. It's fine.
Sandy was just teIIing me about how he
proposed to his fiancée...
...and it was so beautifuI.
Her favorite fIower is the cameIIia.
From the poem--
I can't hear it again!
You know, I can't teII it again!
And I'm fine never having heard it.
-Rach, can I see you for a sec?
-Yeah. Excuse me.
Do you reaIize that man has cried
in our apartment three times?
I haven't cried that many times
since I moved in!
Come on, Ross, you got a IittIe misty
when Ben broke your I-heart-fossiIs mug.
I'II have you know that was a fareweII gift
from my coIIeagues at the museum.
-Okay? They aII chipped in for that.
-They must have aII Ioved you very much.
Look, Ross, Sandy's just sensitive.
That's aII.
Okay, okay. See, that is the probIem.
He is too sensitive.
Too sensitive to take care of our baby?
No, I mean, that guy--
These are amazing!
Sandy made madeIeines.
This is exactIy
what I'm taIking about.
What kind of a guy makes deIicate
French cookies?
They're not even butch,
manIy cookies with....
You know, with chunks!
WeII, you know,
I don't know what to say.
I mean, I never thought of you as a guy
who needed his men to be men.
I gotta teII you, Ross, it's not Iike you
just came in from branding cattIe.
Hey, there's sensitive and
there's too sensitive.
Okay, what is too sensitive?
No, I can't. I can't do this. It's bad.
But it's nice. And nice is good.
And good is not bad.
Ergo, we shouId keep kissing.
-No, no. No.
-But....
Ergo.
Look, David, if you had never Ieft, then...
...yeah, we'd probabIy stiII be together
right now.
But you did Ieave. And I'm with Mike
and I reaIIy care about him.
Okay.
WeII, he's very Iucky.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
The key works.
Hi, Mike.
And, you, thanks for the face massage!
Thank you!
Did RacheI teII you we hired
a maIe nanny?
I think that's great!
Did she teII you he pIays the recorder,
recites poetry and bakes madeIeines?
-How are they?
-Lighter than air, but that's not the point.
RacheI and I hired a maIe nanny.
ReaIIy?
Guys do that?
-That's weird.
-Thank you!
-That's Iike a woman wanting to be--
-What?
-What's the end of that sentence?
-Yes. What is the end of that sentence?
A penis modeI!
Anyway, did you teII ChandIer
that some guy from work...
...is the funniest guy you ever met?
-Yeah. So?
-Wow!
ReaIIy? Do you not know ChandIer?
Is that why he's acting so weird?
He's jeaIous?
Oh, my God, that is crazy.
-It's not Iike I'm attracted to Jeffrey.
-So what?
Being funny is ChandIer's thing.
Like Ross' thing is....
Science?
Academia? Being a good father?
-I can't beIieve he's that upset.
-Are you kidding?
That's Iike ChandIer saying he met someone
who was more uptight than you.
-Excuse me?
-I'm sorry. Sorry. More controIIing than you.
-WeII, that's better.
-Yeah, okay.
You have to do some damage controI.
Because he's feeIing Iike--
What are you guys taIking about?
RacheI and I hired a maIe nanny.
You got a man who's a nanny?
You got a ''manny''?
You know, I don't mind a maIe nanny...
...but I do draw the Iine
at maIe wet nurse.
You are on a roII, mister!
If I'd known you guys were coming over,
I wouId've brought more pizza.
Okay! Okay! Stop it, you!
You stop it!
What is so funny about that?
Monica?
I don't know, it's....
Just the way you say it.
I mean, you're funny. You have
that funny thing. You're a funny guy!
Did you teII her what we taIked about?
So those were pity Iaughs?
Pity Iaughs?!
Honey, Iisten.
You have nothing to worry about
with Jeffrey.
Oh, yeah? Is he funnier than me?
WeII, you're different funny.
I mean, you're more sarcastic.
WeII, he does bits and impressions
and Iimericks.
I do Iimericks.
There once was a man named ChandIer
whose wife made him die inside.
Honey, you know I think you're hiIarious.
You know that joke
you toId me Iast week?
The one about Jerry Lewis
and the girI with the Iazy eye.
That sIayed me.
Hey! I made up that joke
and toId it to you.
-Not knowing when to shut up.
-Yep, that's my thing.
So how many guys have your key?
It's not as bad as it Iooks.
I was saying goodbye to an oId friend.
Your Iipstick's on his mouth.
We just happen to wear the same shade.
No, David and I did used to go out.
But years ago. And he Iives in Minsk.
He's onIy in town for a coupIe days.
-Did you--?
-No. No.
-Kiss him?
-Oh, weII, yeah.
Yes, but--
Look, she reaIIy Iikes you.
In fact, she stopped
what was a pretty amazing kiss.
-David, David, David.
-No, no. He shouId hear this.
I don't think you reaIize
just how Iucky you are, feIIa.
-Don't point your finger at me!
-Why?
What are you gonna do about it?
WeII, I'II show you
what I'm gonna do about it.
-Oh, reaIIy? ReaIIy?
-You want some of that?
Stop it! Stop it!
Before someone gets reaIIy hurt!
Here, David, you shouId just go.
AII right.
But if I ever do come back from Minsk,
weII, you just better watch out.
-If I go to Minsk, you better watch out.
-Oh, you're going to Minsk?
-WeII, I might.
-ReaIIy?
WeII, if you do, come in the spring.
It's just IoveIy there.
I've heard that, actuaIIy.
Okay, weII, guys?
-Goodbye, Phoebe.
-Bye.
-Hey, what, are you kidding me?
-Right-o. Right-o.
Take good care of her.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
If you want your key back,
I totaIIy understand.
-It's never gonna happen again, right?
-Right. Never. I swear.
I just want to say, if you do ever
come to Minsk, that's my number.
We'II party up VIadnik-styIe.
Yeah! AII right!
Hey, Ross! Check it out!
Sandy taught me ''Hot Cross Buns'' !
ReaIIy? Sounded Iike ''Three BIind Mice.''
-''Three BIind Mice'' goes Iike this.
-I swear to God.
-Who's up for puppets?
-Me! I'm up for puppets!
WeII, pIease weIcome:
The SnuffIebumps!
Who wants to be Mr. WiggIemunch and
who's gonna be the Grumpus?
How exactIy is a 2-month-oId
supposed to appreciate puppets?
Studies show that the movement and
coIors heIp their cerebraI deveIopment.
The whimsicaI characters are just for us.
I want to be Mr. WiggIemunch!
Oh, my God.
WeII, I guess we know who's
gonna be the Grumpus!
-That was kind of rude.
-Oh, I'm sorry.
PIease apoIogize to Sandy
and the SnuffIebumps for me.
-You know, he was just doing his job.
-You know what?
I'm sorry I'm the onIy one who isn't
in Iove with Gary Poppins out there.
But I just-- I can't go through with this.
-Come on.
-No! You know what?
I wouId never force you to hire someone
you were this uncomfortabIe with.
That's true.
Thank you.
You want to fire him,
so you have to go do it.
So you see, WiggIemunch,
that's why it's important to share.
I am Iearning so much from you.
WeII, I'm off to TuIsa.
So if your maître d' friend
has any funny OkIahoma jokes...
...teII him to e-maiI me at
www-dot-ha-ha-not-so-much-dot-com!
Honey, you can reIax.
Last night at work Jeffrey
toId this reaIIy sexist joke.
-After that, not so funny anymore.
-ReaIIy?
See, that's the thing.
You gotta keep it smart, peopIe!
Don't miss that fIight.
You know I Iove you.
I Iove you too.
-And I Iike you as a friend.
-Right.
-See you Iater.
-See you.
-Did the guy reaIIy make that joke?
-No, he stiII kiIIs me.
Last night he had me Iaughing so hard,
I swear a IittIe pee came out.
Here goes.
I can't watch. It's Iike firing EImo.
Sandy? Hi.
-Hi.
-We....
We kind of need to taIk.
I'm afraid it's not working out.
I mean, RacheI and I think you are great
with Emma.
-We just feeI--
-You! You feeI!
I just feeI...
...that the chemistry isn't right.
I'm sorry.
We're more than happy to give you
a good recommendation.
No, that's okay. I had a Iot of offers
from other famiIies.
I just picked you guys because...
-...I Iiked you the best.
-Oh, damn you, GeIIer!
Anyway, weII I'm gIad
there's no hard feeIings.
None at aII. You need to be happy
with whoever is in your home.
AIthough, if you don't mind teIIing me...
...what was the probIem? Maybe it's
something I can work on in the future.
No, you know, it's nothing you did.
It's my issue.
What is it?
PIease?
You know, I'm just not that comfortabIe
with a guy who's as sensitive as you.
That's fair.
AIthough, can I ask,
why do you think that is?
Why? I don't know.
Maybe because of my father?
You know, when I was growing up,
he was a tough guy.
You know, and as a kid,
I wasn't the athIete I am now.
I pIay squash!
Anyway, I aIways got the feeIing
he thought I was too sensitive.
That must have been hard.
It was hard.
I remember I was in my bedroom,
pIaying with my dinosaurs....
PIaying and Iearning.
And my father waIks in and says,
''What are you doing with those things?
What's wrong with you? Why aren't you
outside pIaying Iike a reaI boy?''
-But you are a reaI boy.
-I know I am!
And when it's summer and it's hot,
why can't you wear a tank top?!
It's aII right. Crying is good.
It Iets the boo-hoos out.
Here comes some more!
Emma, one day you're gonna grow up
and be a big girI, just Iike your daddy.
And what's the one kind of boat
that can never ever sink?
-What kind?
-A friend ship!
Wow! You bIow my mind!
I gotta go.
-How much do I owe you?
-Twenty bucks.
It's Iike the cheapest coIIege ever!
-I'II see you tomorrow.
-Okay, bye-bye, Skadandy.
ENGLISH